Eddy Tuzolana

Eddytuzolana@icloud.com II 206-379-5643 II 4900 S Thistle Street Seattle, WA 98118

Professional objective

Experienced working in United States for 12 years and most customizing services to provide the best; specialized with expertise in research, performance monitoring, and analysis. Aptitude to increase us timer and traffic. Seeking to perform in the industry a position as a front-end developer to user my excellent coding, organization, strong traffic analysis and demonstrated ability to work autonomously and as part of a team plus a Working knowledge of Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, And JavaScript to accomplish the job requirements for the position.

Skills

- * Data handling skill
- * Excellent communication skills
- * Customer services & Management
- * Good management
- * Positive attitude
- * Hard working ethics
- * HTML, CSS, and JavaScript

- * Excellent interpersonal skills
- * Keyword tracking
- * Strategy development
- * Knowledge of most search engines
- * Speak: French

Education

Tacoma community college
Some college
Currently student radiology technology
* GPA 2.90

University of Kinshasa

Associate degree of science: Mathematics

* GPA 3.00 Year: 08/2007

Experience

Math tutoring

- Science institute the Kasa-Vubu ll Kinshasa 09/2004- 09/2007

Cashier

- Ross dress, LLC ll North Carolina 09/2009-2012

Processor

- American seafood ll Seattle, WA 04/2012 – 04-2013

*Driver*LSG sky chief Seattle, WA
06/2014 – 02/2016

Self employer *Driver & business management* 02/2016 – 09/2021 Seattle, WA

Cleaning company & partnerships Homeaglow 01/2021 – 08/2021

Driver
Wine bow Company, LLC
10-2021 – Currently

Accomplishments

* Maintain high production quality and ratings 5-star for meeting customer satisfaction.

- * 9000 trips after two years of driving for Uber; maintenance and performance of the platforms.
- * Organizations of warehouse and ability to analysis knowledge for development of students on math.
- * Quickly responded to requests for information from clients and colleagues.
- * Updated request documents with daily significant results.
- * Accomplishment daily orders requested to each stop.